Based on the short story by Moreira Campos
故事出自於Moreira Campos
Dogs are Said to See Things
狗目睹了一切
Yeah!
對！
Yes, it's close.
恩，很接近了
How close?
有多近了？
Well, can't you feel the heat?
恩，你們沒有感覺到那熱氣嗎？
So that the sky might turn blue
那天空可能會變藍
So that the planet might be one
而那星球也將成為其中之一
And mankind...
而人類…
See how he likes that?  Can't you see?
你們看他有多喜歡？ 看不出來嗎？
He's really enjoying it.
他真的很享受
- It's me?  - No.
- 我的？ - 不是
Hey...
嘿…
...take that stuff off my face, damn it! Shit!
把那東西從我臉上移開，該死的！媽的！
Asshole!
混蛋！
Attention everyone!
各位注意一下！
Lunch is served!
中餐可以開始享用了！
Hey, get to the back of the line!
嘿，到後面排隊去！
What if you meet someone?
要是你遇見了甚麼人呢？
We never know.
世事難料
Yes, it's better to be prepared.
對呀，最好先有心理準備
- Have a nice meal.  - Thanks.
- 祝你用餐愉快  - 謝謝
- Come here, get in. Come on!  - Thanks.
- 來呀，排這。來嘛！  - 謝了
After all, you're growing up girl.
畢竟，妳也在發育嘛
I wouldn't miss you at all
我一點都不會想你
on a sunny sunday at Beach Park
在海灘公園 一個晴朗的星期天
There's no way I would take you along
我是不可能帶你
for a walk with me at Iguatemi Mall.
一起逛Iguatemi商場
I wouldn't dare facing the embarrassment
我無法面對被
in front of my cool friends from Aldeota.
那些自Aldeota朋友發現的窘境
Because now I hold a high reputation
因為我在現在的社交圈裡
among the high circles of high society.
有一定的地位
I know that the bourgeoisie stinks
雖然我知道那資產階級的腐敗
but it has money to buy perfume.
但那讓我有錢得到我要的
What's more, in the high society
再者，在這資本社會裡
people are cheated on without getting jealous.
人們毫無理由的互相欺騙
I know that the bourgeoisie stinks
雖然我知道那資產階級的腐敗
but it has money to buy perfume.
但那讓我有錢得到我要的
I'm IN, I'm not OUT.
我身陷其中，不像你是局外人
I'm VIP.
我是VIP